<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sumant raj</title>
    <description>Raj Analogue by birth,digital by design.simple during childhood,computerized by configuration.21 years old living vicariously through myself.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll-wing-template/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll-wing-template/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 00:20:16 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 00:20:16 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Engineering A desire Or Just a Career Option.....</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Desire&lt;/code&gt; is infinite, its fulfilment limited, desire is
unlimited in everyone; the power of fulfilment
varies. Thus some are more successful than others
in life.
Engineering a desire or just a career option to get
good life, good wife or good money. It’s what we
always wanted to accomplish, everyone, when
they are young knows what their destiny is, I
thought of becoming the richest person. I think at a
certain point in everyone lives, everything is clear
and everything is possible, They are not afraid to
dream and to yearn for everything they would like
to see happen to them in their lives but as time
passes an inner force begins to convince them that
it will impossible for them to realize their destiny.
But the thing is what we desire is most important
rather than thinking of so called society that if you
are an engineer you have a great future but if you
are a photographer or a hair designer you are good
for nothing, it is painful to listen that but ultimately
we have our self respect and we will be happy in
our life.We desire only the pleasurable not the painful. As
desire increases, so increases the power of
pleasure so the power of pain.
But Pain is inevitable, suffering is optional.
So, follow your dream love your desire.
Future is the extension of present..&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 15:19:45 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll-wing-template/jekyll/update/2016/11/03/welcome-to-jekyll-Copy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll-wing-template/jekyll/update/2016/11/03/welcome-to-jekyll-Copy.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Edward Snowden A Hero Or A Traitor..</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Edward Snowden&lt;/code&gt; A former CIA employee, who supposedly copied
classified information from NSA of mass surveillance programs,
opertaed by NSA. National Security Agency which is involved in
massive collection of private information like phone records internet
traffic in short NSA thwart internet freedom in around every country
even in India too. There was a bug found in indian embassey and
Rajbhawan too. So the question is, Is he is a whistle blower who
gave us reason to not place trust on our goverment system or just a
traitor. He said The NSA has built an infrastructure that allows it to
intercept almost everything. With this capability, the vast majority
of human communications are automatically ingested without
targeting. If I wanted to see your emails or your wife’s phone, all I
have to do is use intercepts. I can get your emails, passwords,
phone records, credit cards. So basically even if you are not doing
anything wrong you are being watched.
Currently he has being given political asylum by Russian goverment
and staying in Russia. So we have to ask ourselve do we want to
live in a world where there is no privacy and therefore no room for
intellectual exploration and creativity. If NO then why is he a traitor?
“ Privacy matters. Privacy is what allows us to determine who we are
and who we want to be.”&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 15:19:45 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll-wing-template/jekyll/update/2016/11/02/welcome-to-jekyll-Copy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll-wing-template/jekyll/update/2016/11/02/welcome-to-jekyll-Copy.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
